// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is the idea being transmitted by the sender to the receiver. It includes three aspects — content, structure, and style.",
    answer: "c. message",
    options: [
      "a. channel",
      "b. feedback",
      "c. message",
      "d. sender"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It is the response or reaction given by the receiver to the sender of the message.",
    answer: "a. feedback",
    options: [
      "a. feedback",
      "b. message",
      "c. receiver",
      "d. sender"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "It is a situation where a communication takes place.",
    answer: "b. Both sender and receiver need to exchange messages.",
    options: [
      "a. The receiver interprets the message.",
      "b. Both sender and receiver need to exchange messages.",
      "c. The sender recognizes the communication style of the other.",
      "d. The sender translates the message into a perceivable form."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It is the exchange of thoughts, messages, or information through speech, signal, writing, or behavior.",
    answer: "b. communication",
    options: [
      "a. channel",
      "b. communication",
      "c. language",
      "d. message"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "This is the group of basic elements of communication. 1. source 2. destination 3. medium 4. language",
    answer: "c. 2 and 3 only",
    options: [
      "a. 1234",
      "b. 123 only",
      "c. 2 and 3 only",
      "d. 1 and 2 only"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "It is characterized by being a “selective” listener.",
    answer: "b. Rina changes the subject from time to time.",
    options: [
      "a. Jay displays a blank look.",
      "b. Rina changes the subject from time to time.",
      "c. Tom asks questions to seek greater understanding.",
      "d. Ana gives feedback to acknowledge the speaker’s emotion"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The most effective form of communication is always through words.",
    answer: "c. No, because words can inhibit people from saying/declaring the truth.",
    options: [
      "a. Yes, because through words we are allowed to explain ourselves.",
      "b. Yes, because there are always words to express what we want to say.",
      "c. No, because words can inhibit people from saying/declaring the truth.",
      "d. No, because words can be abused by people and can cause hurt or confusion."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It is defined as any communication that uses spoken or written words to convey a message.",
    answer: "c. verbal communication",
    options: [
      "a. non-verbal communication",
      "b. oral communication",
      "c. verbal communication",
      "d. written communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "It is a type of communication that does NOT use words in expressing a message.",
    answer: "a. non-verbal communication",
    options: [
      "a. non-verbal communication",
      "b. oral communication",
      "c. verbal communication",
      "d. written communication"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "It is the nature of communication. 1. Communication is a process. 2. Communication portrays sympathy. 3. Communication occurs between two or more people. 4. Communication can be expressed through words or actions.",
    answer: "d. 1 and 2 only",
    options: [
      "a. 1234",
      "b. 134 only",
      "c. 2 and 3 only",
      "d. 1 and 2 only"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "It is the meaning of the statement 'Communication is a process'.",
    answer: "c. Communication is dynamic, ongoing and continuous.",
    options: [
      "a. Communication consists of discrete and separate acts.",
      "b. Communication has clear beginning and ending points.",
      "c. Communication is dynamic, ongoing and continuous.",
      "d. Communication resembles still pictures more than a motion picture."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "It refers to the communicator or the source of information.",
    answer: "d. sender",
    options: [
      "a. inceptor",
      "b. originator",
      "c. receiver",
      "d. sender"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The following are forms of non-verbal communication EXCEPT...",
    answer: "a. e-mail",
    options: [
      "a. e-mail",
      "b. road signs",
      "c. eye blink",
      "d. thumbs up sign"
     ]
  },
];
